{
    "id": "9cc5bbecc6b24bddbf837de9af1fc441",
    "title": "Gap Fills",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You will have an accident if you ………………. on driving like that.",
            "description": "In the first conditional, we use a simple present tense in the if-clause and will + first form of the verb in the main clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "goes",
                "went"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4f73fdd33e54438ba13fceb99c412583"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘The door bell is ringing.’ ‘I …………………..’",
            "description": "The simple future is used to announce decisions that are taken at the moment of speaking. ",
            "answers": [
                "am going",
                "am going to go",
                "will go"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8f08bfedf6eb4ff1b6f2fe131ee49f3d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… my parents next week.",
            "description": "The present continuous is used to talk about pre-planned future events. ",
            "answers": [
                "visit",
                "will visit",
                "am visiting"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bf870b6d252547ae9b2633f9eb1e115a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Will it be all right if I …………………….. an extra night?",
            "description": "In the first conditional, we use a simple present tense in the if-clause and will + first form of the verb in the main clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "stay",
                "stayed",
                "had stayed"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b36a08e97b554116a798f725efbe2722"
        },
        {
            "question": "She didn’t get the promotion ………………………. working hard.",
            "description": "Before an ing form we use a preposition. In spite of is a preposition. ",
            "answers": [
                "however",
                "in spite of",
                "though"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b2d12cb7a772492db554bc515512a497"
        },
        {
            "question": "The deer was ……………………. by a car.",
            "description": "Stricken is the past participle of strike. ",
            "answers": [
                "struck",
                "strucked",
                "stricken"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ec52ef39435349368a8bdb5063471a4f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Those who know the answer should …………………… their hand.",
            "description": "Raise is transitive rise is intransitive.",
            "answers": [
                "rise",
                "raise"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cea71fe8d4484129aba206f2306c1fb6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Much water has ………………….. under the bridge.",
            "description": "Flown is the past participle is fly. Flowed is the past participle of flow. ",
            "answers": [
                "flowed",
                "flown"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c7c87b1289014dd6b31261430870449c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had met him before he ……………………. to Germany.",
            "description": "Flew is the past participle of fly. ",
            "answers": [
                "flew",
                "flowed",
                "flown"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "62452caece0848d0a53b3a70a7be8ddd"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ……………………. men were taken to hospital.",
            "description": "Wounded means injured. ",
            "answers": [
                "wound",
                "wounded"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "741bbfcb0e584455b4da441e9fa4880d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She got married ……………………… her colleague.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bb206cbb285a4658880d0158ac160d01"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I reached there, I could see that they …………………..",
            "description": "The past perfect is used for the earlier of the two past actions. ",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "have left",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5f71a29c4e864d84a48e3c5601f2d128"
        }
    ]
}